{
  "module": {
    "number": 1,
    "name": "Level-one",
    "questions": 10,
    "revision": "HUH"
  },
  "questions": [
    {
      "number": 1,
      "question": "What food is this?",
      "answers": [
        "Banana",
        "Apple",
        "Strawberry",
        "Blueberry"
      ],
      "correct_answer": 1,
      "hint":"Yellow Fruit"
    },
    {
      "number": 2,
      "question": "What food is this?",
      "answers": [
        "Pancake",
        "Waffle",
        "Scones",
        "Nuggets"
      ],
      "correct_answer": 2,
      "hint":"Heart shaped"
    },
        {
      "number": 3,
      "question": "What food is this?",
      "answers": [
        "Taco",
        "Steak",
        "Pie",
        "Mac'N Cheese"
      ],
      "correct_answer": 3,
      "hint":"Comes in a casserole"
    },
        {
      "number": 4,
      "question": "What food is this?",
      "answers": [
        "Corn Flakes",
        "Mushrooms",
        "Ceasar Salad",
        "Yoghurt"
      ],
      "correct_answer": 3,
      "hint":"A type of salad"
    },
        {
      "number": 5,
      "question": "What food is this?",
      "answers": [
        "Tater Tots",
        "Bread",
        "Fajitas",
        "Salmon"
      ],
      "correct_answer": 4,
      "hint": "Comes from the sea"
    },
        {
      "number": 6,
      "question": "What food is this?",
      "answers": [
        "P&J Sandwich",
        "Enchiladas",
        "Smores",
        "Chicken wings"
      ],
      "correct_answer": 3,
      "hint": "Dessert"
    },
        {
      "number": 7,
      "question": "What food is this?",
      "answers": [
        "Lasagne",
        "BBQ Ribs",
        "Apple Pie",
        "Chocolate Chip Cookies"
      ],
      "correct_answer": 4,
      "hint":"Dessert"
    },
        {
      "number": 8,
      "question": "What food is this?",
      "answers": [
        "Beef Stroganof",
        "Spagetthi and Meatballs",
        "Chicken and Rice",
        "Pizza"
      ],
      "correct_answer": 1,
      "hint":"Pasta and Meat"
    },
        {
      "number": 9,
      "question": "What food is this?",
      "answers": [
        "Nachos",
        "Hot Dogs",
        "Cheese Burger",
        "Turkey"
      ],
      "correct_answer": 2,
      "hint":"Sausage"
    },
        {
      "number": 10,
      "question": "What food is this?",
      "answers": [
        "Spaghetti and meatballs",
        "Fried chicken",
        "Beef stir fry",
        "Burritos"
      ],
      "correct_answer": 4,
      "hint":"looks like a taco"
    }
    
  ]
}